Christopher Corbin

Rochester NY

Experienced Network Security Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the telecommunications and financial industrys. Skilled in Cisco equipment including Routers, Switches, Firewalls and Proxies. Additional security experience with various other Firewall vendors including Palo Alto, Fortinet, Juniper, as well as SIEM architectures such as HP Arcsight. Network Architecture design work including regression testing with various Cisco and Juniper equipment. Additional years of troubleshooting experience with Session Initiation Protocol (SIP), Open Shortest Path First (OSPF), and TDM technologies. VoIP experience including support of 3rd party systems over provider networks and configuration of SIP trunking systems and IP PBXs. Strong information technology professional with a Bachelor's of Science focused in Telecommunications Engineering from Rochester Institute of Technology. See less of summary

EXPERIENCE

Senior Information Security Engineer

U.S. Bank Jan 2018

Network Engineer II

Windstream Jun 2012

VPN Engineer

PAETEC

Jun 2010 - Jan 2012

Turned up and troubleshot customer MPLS networks from a carrier grade environment.

Network Operations Technician

PAETEC

Jun 2007 - Jun 2009

Troubleshot customer issues on a carrier network ranging from T1 facility issues to video conferencing as well as VoIP and TDM calling issues.

EDUCATION

Rochester Institute of Technology

Bachelor's of Science 2002 - 2007

WEBSITES

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/talent/hire/622849074/discover/recruiterSearch/profile/AEMAAAskUOcBduk7wD9qMqJpePZIx6ZK9u3ga7I

Source: LinkedIn